<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="Creating JIRA Bugs">
    <title>Creating JIRA Bug in TMS and JIRA configuration</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <p>This page describes how TMS can write bugs in JIRA and how to configure JIRA fields.</p>
            <p>
                TMS dynamically reads JIRA information fields and uses this information to populate the
                create bug widget in TMS. It reads the name of the field and then adds this as a field that the user can
                use to enter data into in TMS. The fields are as follows:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>Component/s</li>
                <li>Fix Version/s</li>
                <li>Team Name</li>
                <li>Found In Release</li>
                <li>Found in Sprint</li>
                <li>Delivered in Sprint</li>
            </ul>
            <p>JIRA has pre-defined by default i.e. "Component/s" or "Fix Version/s". These will always exist</p>
            <p>If the field does not exists then it will not be displayed and no data is retrieved.</p>
            <p>If the JIRA field is created with the above field names then TMS  will read these fields and get its meta data.</p>
            <p>If the field does not exist then it will not be displayed and no data is retrieved.</p>

            <p><b>However in JIRA fields can be specified as required fields. TMS will automatically pick these up and
                add them to the create bug feature.
            This means that additional fields specific to that project will be displayed and if set will override
                the optional values above and force the user to enter data.</b></p>

            <p><b>When a project is changed in TMS</b> it will query JIRA for its metadata. TMS uses a user called <b>lciadm100</b> in JIRA
                to access and view project data. In cases where the user in TMS receives a message saying it could not retrieve this data. This maybe an access issue with lciadm100</p>
            <image href="../resources/jira/no_meta_data.png"/>
            <p><b>It is required in JIRA to add lciadm100 user as a developer to the project in question and possibly administrator access to the project. This will allow TMS to read the meta data</b></p>


            <p>To create a JIRA bug in TMS the user must be in the test execution screen of the their test plan. If TMS has a project selected then the "Create bug"
            button will appear otherwise it will remain hidden. When the "Create bug" button is clicked then it will open the create bug widget.</p>
            <image href="../resources/jira/created_bug_button.png"/>
            <p>Once the user has filled in the required fields then by clicking the "Create" button it will create the bug in JIRA.</p>
            <image href="../resources/jira/create_bug_widget.png"/>
            <p>If the values are not entered or invalid the effected option will be highlighted</p>
            <image href="../resources/jira/invalid_values.png"/>
            <p>Finally it will then be populated in the defect box in order to save the execution</p>
            <image href="../resources/jira/created_bug.png"/>

            <title>Attachments</title>
            <p>TMS allows the user to attach a file when creating a bug. Click on the attachments and choose a file.</p>
            <image href="../resources/jira/attachments.png"/>

        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
