<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<task id="Overview">
    <title>Test Case Import/Export</title>
    <taskbody>
        <section>
            <title>Export</title>
            <p>TMS provides the user with multiple export options:
                <ul>
                    <li>TMS Users are given the choice to "Generate Report" from "Select a Test Case" page provided that
                        the search did not return 0 test cases.
                        <p>Users have a number of options to choose from:</p>
                    </li>
                    <ol>
                        <li>
                            <b>Create General Acceptance Test (GAT) Report (.docx)*</b>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <b>Create Test Specification Report (.docx)*</b>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <b>Create Report that can be re-imported (.xlsx)</b>
                        </li>
                    </ol>
                </ul>
                <li>
                    The "Quick Search" field, quick filters and the advanced search can be used to filter the test cases needed for generating a report.
                    <p><image href="../../resources/export/generateReport1.png"/></p>
                    <p><image href="../../resources/export/generateReport2.png"/></p>
                </li>
                <p>*If you select either of these options you will be given the option to include file details in the
                    report (this refers to any file attached to the test case).
                </p>
                <image href="../../resources/export/generateReportOptions.png"/>
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>What does the exported file look like ?</title>
            <p>The exported test case will appear like follows:
            </p>
            <image href="../../resources/import/import.png"/>
            <p>In order to view this correctly the user must format the cell for text wrapping. In microsoft Excel :
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    Right click on a single cell or all cells you wish to wrap.
                </li>
                <li>
                    Click
                    <b>Format Cells...</b>
                </li>
                <li>
                    Click the tab called
                    <b>Alignment</b>
                </li>
                <li>
                    In the
                    <b>Text Control</b>
                    section click the checkbox
                    <b>Wrap text</b>
                </li>
            </ul>
            <p>
                <b>Test Steps</b>
            </p>
            <p>
                As seen above all test steps are contained inside one cell. This is due to the complexity of the
                data.
            </p>
            <p>Each data set is labeled specifically/independently so the parser can collect the data and convert to
                test steps
                inside the application.
                <b>Each data set must end with a newline</b>.
            </p>
            <p>
                This structure allows the user to only add the labels required. So, for example, if there is no test data
                then simply omitting the label will ensure it will not be added.
                The user can have multiple test steps and multiple verify steps. For each test step there is a
                closing sequence of characters
                <b>*%]</b>
                This must be added to the end of the test step, otherwise, it will be merged into the previous test step
                or it may not be interpreted at all.
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    $$$TESTSTEP$$$ Enter user data here $$$
                </li>
                <li>
                    $$$TESTDATA$$$ Enter user data here $$$
                </li>
                <li>
                    $$$VERIFYSTEP$$$ Enter user data here $$$
                </li>
            </ul>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Import</title>
            <p>Test Management System (TMS) supports the importing of a test case. TMS excel report (Create Report that can be re-imported (.xlsx)) has been setup with
                the ability to be re-imported to TMS.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Note:</b>
                <p>When you import a test case file all test cases that have the same test case id as those contained in
                    the file will be updated.
                    Therefore, it's important to check that your test case id's are correct to avoid accidental
                    overwrites.
                    If a new test case id is detected during file import TMS will create a new test case.
                </p>
                <p>For optional parameters such as contexts, groups, execution type etc. , if the incorrect options are
                    entered this will not fail validation but the field will be empty as the system will be unable to
                    map them to the correct values.
                    These types of values are case insensitive.
                </p>
            </p>
        </section>
        <prereq>
            <ul>
                <li>Login to TMS using your corporate userId</li>
                <li>Navigate to "Select a test case"</li>
                <li>Choose "Import Test Case" from dropdown as shown below</li>
                <image href="../../resources/import/tmsUserImportTestCase.png"/>
            </ul>
        </prereq>
        <steps>
            <step id="1">
                <cmd>Select the file you wish to import</cmd>
                <info><p>Make sure that
                    <b>empty cells in a row contain a blank string</b>
                    otherwise import will fail. The user will
                    need to click on the cell and add a blank space.</p><p>
                    Excel's backend does not store empty cells in its xml.
                    This causes data to be added into the wrong columns. Test cases will not be imported if a row does
                    not
                    have the correct number of columns.
                    </p>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="2">
                <cmd>Click import</cmd>
                <info>Upon a successful import the user will get a notification that the test cases have been imported
                    and all
                    the test cases that have been added will be displayed in a table.
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
        <result>
            <b>Successful Import</b>
            <image href="../../resources/import/success.png"/>
            <b>Failed Import</b>
            <image href="../../resources/import/failure.png"/>
        </result>
    </taskbody>
</task>
