<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<task id="Overview">
    <title>Test Case Versioning</title>
    <taskbody>
        <section>
            <title>Overview</title>
            <p>TMS takes a very simple approach to test case versioning. Versions are controlled by the review process.
                Test case versions are incremented
                automatically once they have been approved.
                Test cases are either approved as major or minor version.
                Test Case versions are approved either by:
                <ul>
                    <li>an individual assigned as a reviewer</li>
                    <li>a member of the review group* assigned to review a test case</li>
                </ul>
            </p>
            <p>
                *A review group is a list of users that can approve the test case.
            </p>
            <p>The test case version can be found from the test case details page:</p>
            <p>
                <image href="../../resources/versioning/test_case_version.png"/>
            </p>
            <p>The Version drop down allows users to select previous versions of
                test cases to see what changes were made. Previous approved versions cannot be edited.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>To create a new test case version the user can click edit on the test case they wish to create a new version of. The system will
                    create a
                    new version for editing.
                </b>
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Relationship between Test Case Versions and Test Case Status</title>
            <p>The test case version is automatically updated once it has been approved.</p>
            <p>There is no change to the test case version if it is rejected.</p>
            <p>There are a total five possible states in which a test case can be in:</p>
            <ol>
                <li>
                    <b>Preliminary:</b>
                    The initial state for a test case when it is
                    in editing mode.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Review:</b>
                    Test case development is complete and test case is
                    ready to be reviewed by reviewers.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Approved:</b>
                    The test case has been reviewed and updates
                    completed.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Rejected:</b>
                    A rejected test case can be edited by the user and
                    re-sent for review.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Cancelled:</b>
                    The test case review has been cancelled. A cancelled test case can be edited by the user and
                    re-sent for review.
                </li>
            </ol>
        </section>
        <prereq>
            <ul>
                <li>Login to the TMS system using your corporate user Id</li>
                <li>From the Quick menu section select “My Reviews”</li>
            </ul>
            <image href="../../resources/versioning/tmsUserReviews.png"/>
            <p>
                This will then show the user the list of test cases they can review. As shown below.
            </p>
            <image href="../../resources/versioning/tmsUserMyReviews.png"/>
        </prereq>
        <steps>
            <step id="1">
                <cmd>Select the test case Id of the test case you wish to review</cmd>
                <p>

                </p>
            </step>
            <step id="2">
                <cmd>Click on the "Approve" icon</cmd>
                <info>
                    <p>
                        <image href="../../resources/versioning/test_case_approve.png"/>
                    </p>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="3">
                <cmd>Click on the appropriate response for the review</cmd>
                <info>
                    <p>
                        <image href="../../resources/versioning/test_case_approve_dialog.png"/>
                    </p>

                    <p>
                        <b>1) Approve Minor Version</b>
                        - Sets the status of the test case to approved and increases the version for example from 0.1 to
                        0.2.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        <b>2) Approve Major Version</b>
                        - Sets the status of the test case to approved and increases the version for example from 0.1 to
                        1.0.
                        The status for 1.0 is set to approved.
                    </p>
                    <p>
                        <b>3) Reject</b>
                        - Sets the status to rejected and the user can then re-edit the test case.
                    </p>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
        <steps>
            <step id="1">
                <cmd>Select the test case Id of the test case you wish to cancel its review</cmd>
                <p>

                </p>
            </step>
            <step id="2">
                <cmd>Click on the "Cancel Review" icon</cmd>
                <info>
                    <p>
                        <image href="../../resources/versioning/test_case_approve.png"/>
                    </p>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
        <result>
            <p>If approved the version will be incremented according to type of approval major/minor.</p>
            <p>If rejected or cancelled the version will be unchanged.</p>
        </result>
    </taskbody>
</task>