<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="Overview">
    <title>Test Case Information</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
           <title>What is a test Case ?</title>
                <p>TAF TM allows a user to map out their test cases. Please see below for a description of each attribute that may be assigned to a test case.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Requirement ID(s)</b>: The unique ID of one or more user Epics or stories. (e.g. In case
                            of OSS, it is the JIRA ID of the story).
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Test Case ID</b>: Unique ID assigned to your test case that should NEVER be changed.
                            Recommendation is to use a reference to parent requirement of feature. E.g
                            TORF-1234_AddNode_Func1
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Title</b>: Title of the test case.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Description</b>: A general description of the purpose of the test case.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Pre-Condition</b>: Environmental and state conditions that must be fulfilled before the
                            component or system can be
                            executed with a particular test or test procedure.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Feature</b>: Corresponds to the feature/feature area i.e. PM , FM, CM  where test cases were written.
                            A feature is a unit of work that fulfills a requirement.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Components</b>: The component is the underlying module of a feature.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Type</b>: A group of test activities aimed at testing a component or system focused on a
                            specific test
                            objective, i.e. functional test, usability test, regression test etc. A test type may take
                            place on one
                            or more test levels or test phases. (e.g. Functional, Performance, Workflow, etc).
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Priority</b>: The level of (business) importance assigned to a test case.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Group</b>: This can be the test phase the test case is applicable for or . E.g. KGB, GAT.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Context</b>: The technology used to interface to the System Under Test.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Execution Type</b>: Manual or Automated Test Case.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Automation Candidate</b>: Select whether this Test Case is a candidate for automation.
                            Options available are 'Yes' and 'No'.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Status</b>: State of the design of the test case specification.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Reviewer</b>: Name of person/group assigned to review this test case.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Intrusive</b>: Intrusive testing: can be considered a type of interrupt testing, which is
                            used to test how well a system reacts to intrusions and interrupts to its normal workflow.
                        </p>
                        <p>Non-Intrusive testing: that is transparent to the software under test, i.e., does not change
                            its timing or processing characteristics.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Reason</b>: The reason for test case.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Team</b>: The name of the team name who originally wrote the test case.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Suite</b>: The name of the suite to which the test case has been added.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Test Step / Verify Step</b>: Each test case will have one to many test step/verify step
                            pairs.
                        </p>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <p><b>Files</b>: This is a utility to store files for a test case. The supported file types are "txt", "csv", "py", "sh", "bash", "pyw", "pyo", "pyc", "pyd",
                            "log", "zip", "gzip", "png", "jpg", "gz".
                        </p>
                    </li>
                </ul>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>
                <b>How to track changes to test cases:</b>
            </title>

            <p>At the test case level all changes to test cases are tracked via the
                audit functionality.
                This means that for every change made to a test
                case the differences to
                the previous test case are stored in the TMS
                database.
            </p>
            <p>
                These changes are visible via the audit link in TMS that opens a sliding panel as
                follows:
            </p>

            <p>
                <image href="../../resources/versioning/test_case_audit.png"/>
            </p>

            <p>As can be seen above, every change is tracked and the user and time are recorded</p>

            <p>
                <b>NB:</b>
                Currently the details of each change are stored in the TMS
                database.
                The ability to switch to a particular
                audit has not been implemented
                in the TMS UI.
            </p>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
