<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="TMS-SearchTestCases">
    <title>File 2</title>
    <conbody>
        <section id="testCaseFormHeader">
            <title>Test Case Results</title>
            <p>Lists all the test cases associated with the selected product. Results can be filtered using the 'Quick Search' or 'Advanced Search' features.</p>
            <p>Selected test cases can be added to a test campaign or exported to a text file using the links provided</p>
        </section>
        <section id="advancedSearchHeader">
            <title>Advanced Search</title>
            <p>Multiple criteria can be added to further refine the search.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="moreButton">
            <title>More Button</title>
            <p>Displays the menu for test case 'Advanced Search' feature.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="criteria">
            <title>Advanced Search Criteria</title>
            <p>Add multiple criteria to search test cases by.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="projectsDropdown">
            <title>Select Project</title>
            <p>Filter test cases by specific project or select 'All Projects'.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="resultsLinks">
            <title>Links</title>
            <p>'Saved Search' : Allows users to save the search that they have used.</p>
            <p>'Search Menu' : Select the previously saved search url to use that search again.</p>
            <p>'Add to Test Campaign' : Select checkboxes of test cases to add to a test campaign. Test campaign can be selected in the next step.</p>
            <p>'Generate Report' : Exports all test cases from the results table to a text document.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="icons">
            <title>Icons Description</title>
            <p>'Create Test Case': Click to create a new test case.</p>
            <p>'Test Plans': Navigate to view all test plans.</p>
            <p>'Requirements': Navigate to view the requirements for the selected project. If 'All Projects'
                is selected, no requirements will be shown..</p>
        </section>
        <section id="resultsHeader">
            <title>Results</title>
            <p>This table lists all the test cases returned from the advanced search. Click the check box beside each test case to be added to the test campaign.
                Use the 'Add Selected' button to add all the selected test cases to the test campaign.</p>
        </section>
        <section id="results">
            <title>Results</title>
            <p>Use the advanced search widget to search for test cases. Multiple test cases can be selected and added
                to the test campaign using the 'Add Selected' button.</p>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>