<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<task id="Create Test Campaign">
    <title>Create Test Campaign</title>
    <taskbody>
        <prereq>
            <li>User should be logged in</li>
            <li>User should Select "Create Test Campaign" option from Quick Links</li>
        </prereq>
        <steps>
            <step id="1">
                <cmd>Enter Test Campaign Details</cmd>
                <info>
                         <p>Test Campaign Parameters that should be specified include:</p>
                        <sl>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Test Campaign name</b>
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Description of test campaign:</b> the purpose and scope of test
                            campaign
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Feature:</b> (Optional) the features that all test cases in campaign should fall under.
                            Can be left blank if unsure and it wont limit what test cases can be added
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Component:</b> (Optional) the components that all test cases in campaign should fall under.
                            Can be left blank if unsure and it wont limit what test cases can be added
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Drop:</b> the test campaign is applicable for. This
                            field is automatically populated from information in jira.
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Environment:</b> the specific environment the tests are planned
                            for
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Start and End dates:</b> for tracking purposes
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>PS-From and PS-To:</b> (Optional) Depending upon the drop which is selected,required ISO's should be given here.
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Guide Revision:</b> (Optional) Required Guide Revision should be given here
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>SED Revision:</b> (Optional) Required SED Revision should be given here
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Other Dependent SW:</b> (Optional) Required Other Dependent SW should be given here
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Node Type and Version:</b> (Optional) Required Node Type and Version should be given here
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>SoV Status:</b> (Optional) Required Sov status should be given here. (Recommended values are Compliant, Non Compliant, Partially Compliant)
                        </sli>
                        <sli>
                            <b>Comment:</b> (Optional) Comment should be given here
                        </sli>
                        </sl>


                    <p>
                        <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testcampaign_create_page.png"/>
                        <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testcampaign_create_page1.png"/>
                        <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testcampaign_create_page1-1.png"/>
                    </p>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="2">
                <cmd>Assign test cases to test campaign</cmd>
                <info><p>Test cases need to be assigned to the given test campaign.
                    Use the “Add Multiple” option to find the test cases and add them to the
                    campaign.
                    </p>
                    <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testcampaign_create_page2.png"/>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="3">
                <cmd>Find &amp; Select test cases to add to test campaign</cmd>
                <info><p>This provides the user with the search criteria to find your test
                    cases. Multiple search criteria can be applied here to find your
                    test cases.
                    </p>
                </info>
                <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testcampaign_create_add_criteria.png"/>
                <info>
                    <p>In this example a search finds all test cases where the Component
                        field contains the word "Deployment".</p>
                    <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testcampaign_create_select.png"/>
                    <ol>
                        <li>Select the Test Cases you want to Add</li>
                        <li>Click "Add Selected" to add them to your test plan</li>
                        <li>Click the Highlighted arrow to return to Test Plan Create Page</li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="4">
                <cmd>Assign Test Cases to a User</cmd>
                <info>
                    <p>This can be done using the
                        “Assign to User Option”. Select the test cases in the test campaign
                        create/edit page and assign them to users. Corporate user id’s can
                        be used and they will be matched against the corporate ldap server.
                        The users will receive an e-mail with a link to the test campaign.
                        <b>NB.</b> When assigning test cases via Edit Test Campaign,
                        always ensure to save the test campaign, otherwise the emails will
                        not be sent.
                    </p>
                </info>
                <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testcampaign_assign_testcase.png"/>
            </step>
            <step id="5">
                <cmd>Complete Test Campaign Creation-Click "Create"</cmd>
                <info>When you are happy with the content of your test campaign use the
                    "Create" button to complete the creation of the test campaign.
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
        <result>
            <b>TMS Inbox</b>
            <p>When the Test Campaign has been created, test cases assigned to
                users are visible in their Inbox.
            </p>
            <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testcampaign_inbox.png"/>
        </result>
    </taskbody>
</task>

