<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="Overview">
    <title>Test Campaign Groups</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <title>Introduction</title>
            <ul>
                <li>Test Campaign Groups allow users to create and add their test campaigns to one or more groups.</li>
                <li>It will then calculate the test case execution data for each test campaign and give an overall
                    value.
                </li>
            </ul>
                <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testCampaignGroups.png"/>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Adding a Group</title>
            <p>To add a group the user can click on the "Add Group" button and enter the name of the group to be added.</p>
            <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testCampaignGroupsMenuBar.png"/>
            <title>Adding a Test Campaign to a Group</title>
            <p>In the test campaign edit screen a new component called group will allow users to associate the test
                campaign with a group. This is an optional field.</p>
            <image href="../../resources/testcampaigns/testCampaignGroupsEdit.png"/>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Search for a Group</title>
            <ul>
            <li>If users enter search criteria the url will be updated with the search criteria.
               <li>If the user specifies the exact name of the folder it will auto select the group to display to the user.
                   e.g. /#tm/testCampaignGroups?name~test</li>
            </li>
            </ul>

        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Edit a Test Campaign Group</title>
            <ul>
                Users may edit the name of a test campaign group by following these steps:
                <li>Select the test campaign group you wish to edit</li>
                <li> Click on the edit icon</li>
                <li>Enter the new name and click 'Edit'</li>
            </ul>
            <image href="../../resources/testCampaignGroup/editTestCampaignGroup.png" />
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Delete a Test Campaign Group</title>
            <ul>
                Users may delete a test campaign group by following these steps:
                <li>Select the test campaign group you wish to edit</li>
                <li> Click on the delete icon</li>
                <li>Confirm that you wish to proceed with the delete</li>
            </ul>
            <image href="../../resources/testCampaignGroup/deleteTestCampaignGroup.png" />
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Copy Url for a Test Campaign Group</title>
            <ul>
                Users may copy the url for a test campaign group by following these steps:
                <li>Select the test campaign group you wish to copy url for</li>
                <li>Click on the copy link icon</li>
            </ul>
            <image href="../../resources/testCampaignGroup/copyURLTestCampaignGroup.png" />
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
