<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="Administrator Permissions">
    <title>Administrator Permissions</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Introduction</b>
                </title>
                <p>Test Management System (TMS) currently caters to two types of users:
                    <ul>
                        <li>TM Users</li>
                        <li>Admin users</li>
                    </ul>
                    The majority of admin specific functionality can be accessed via the administrator page.
                    <p>To access this page, login and select the 'Admin' option from the user menu.</p>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <image href="../../resources/admin/adminOption.png"/>
                </p>
            </section>
            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>User Access</b>
                </title>
                <p>User Access allows the current administrator to assign a non admin user administrator permissions.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the user</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the table will remove the user</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageUserAccess.png"/>
                </p>
            </section>

            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Product</b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin have the ability to add/edit a Product in TMS. Both the Name and External Id are mandatory
                    fields.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the product</li>
                    <li>To Edit click on the product you wish to edit, then fill in the fields and click the edit button</li>
                    <li>Refresh button on the table will refresh the list of products</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the table will remove the product</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageProduct.png"/>
                </p>
            </section>

            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Features</b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin have the ability to add/edit a Feature in TMS. Both the Product and Feature Name must be
                    specified.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the feature</li>
                    <li>To Edit click on the feature you wish to edit, then fill in the fields and click the edit button</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the table will remove the feature</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageFeatures.png"/>
                </p>
            </section>

            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Components</b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin can add/edit a component in TMS by specifying the Product, Feature and Component names.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the Component</li>
                    <li>To Edit click on the component you wish to edit, then fill in the  name field and click the edit button</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the table will remove the Component.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageComponents.png"/>
                </p>
            </section>

            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Test Types</b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin have the ability to add/edit a Test Type in TMS. Both the Product and Test Type must be
                    specified.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the Test Type</li>
                    <li>To Edit click on the Test Type you wish to edit, then fill in the name field and click the edit button</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the table will remove the Test Type.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageTestTypes.png"/>
                </p>
            </section>
            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Groups</b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin have the ability to add/edit a Group in TMS. This group is used to pool test cases together.Both the
                    Product and Group Name must be
                    specified.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the Group</li>
                    <li>To Edit click on the Group you wish to edit, then fill in the name field and click the edit button</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the table will remove the Group.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageGroups.png"/>
                </p>
            </section>
            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Review Group</b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin have the ability to add/edit a Review Group in TMS. This group contains a collection of users who
                    can carry out a review on any test case to which the group are assigned.
                    Both the name of the user you wish to add and the group to which you want to add the user must be
                    specified.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the Review Group</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the review group table will remove the Review Group.</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the user table will remove the user from the selected Review Group.</li>
                    <li>Edit option is given when you select a group form the review group table and you can add more
                        members to it or change the group name.
                    </li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                    <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageReviewGroup.png"/>
                </p>
            </section>
            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Projects</b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin have the ability to add/edit a Project to TMS. The Product, Project Name and External Id must be
                    specified.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the Project</li>
                    <li>To Edit click on the Project you wish to edit, then fill in the fields and click the edit button</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the table will remove the Project.</li>
                </ul>
                <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageProject.png"/>
            </section>
            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Teams</b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin have the ability to add/edit a Team in TMS.The Product, Feature and Team Name must be
                    specified.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the Team</li>
                    <li>To Edit click on the Team you wish to edit, then fill in the team name field and click the edit button</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the table will remove the Team.</li>
                </ul>
                <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageTeam.png"/>
            </section>
            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>
                        Suites
                    </b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin have the ability to add/edit a Test Suite to TMS.The Product, Feature and Suite Name must be
                    specified.
                </p>
                <b>What is the difference between test suite and group ?</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the Team</li>
                    <li>To Edit click on the Suite you wish to edit, then fill in the suite name field and click the edit button</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the table will remove the Team.</li>
                </ul>
                <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageSuites.png"/>
            </section>
            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Test Campaign Group</b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin have the ability to add/edit a Test Campaign Group to TMS. The Product and Test Campaign Name must be
                    specified.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the Test Campaign Gtoup</li>
                    <li>Delete button on the table will remove the Test Campaign Group.</li>
                    <li>To Edit click on the Test Campaign Group you wish to edit, then fill in the name field and click the edit button</li>
                </ul>
                <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageTestCampaignGroup.png"/>
            </section>
            <section>
                <title>
                    <b>Product Drop</b>
                </title>
                <p>Admin have the ability to add a Drop to a Product in TMS. The Product and Drop must be
                    specified.
                </p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Add button underneath the name field will add the Drop</li>
                </ul>
                <image href="../../resources/admin/adminPageDrop.png"/>
            </section>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>
                <b>Ability to delete a test Case</b>
            </title>
            <p>Admin can remove a test case in TMS by following the steps outlined below</p>
            <ul>
                <li>Login</li>
                <li>Navigate to 'Select a test Case' and open the test case you wish to delete</li>
                <li>Click on delete to remove the test case and click 'Remove' on the prompt to confirm the deletion
                </li>
            </ul>
            <p>
                <image href="../../resources/admin/adminDeleteTestCase.png"/>
            </p>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
